http://www.wkgc.co.uk/terms-of-use/

Your browser is not supported. Please update it.
Twitter
terms Of UseIntroductionThese terms and conditions govern your use of this website; by using this website, you accept these terms and conditions in full. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, do not use this website.Intellectual property rightsUnless otherwise stated, we or our licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. Subject to the licence below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved.Licence to use websiteYou may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions below. You must not:(a) Republish material from this website (including republication on another website);(b) Sell, rent or otherwise sub-license material on the website;(c) Reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on this website for a commercial purpose; edit or otherwise modify any material on the website;(d) Redistribute material from this website except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistributionWhere content is specifically made available for redistribution, it may only be redistributed for non-commercial use.Limitations of liabilityThe information on this website is provided free-of-charge, and you acknowledge that it would be unreasonable to hold us liable in respect of this website and the information on this website.Whilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up-to-date.To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions (including, without limitation, the conditions implied by law of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and the use of reasonable care and skill).Our liability is limited and excluded to the maximum extent permitted under applicable law. We will not be liable for any direct or indirect loss or damage arising under these terms and conditions or in connection with this website, whether arising in tort, contract, or otherwise. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing exclusion, we will not be liable for any loss of profit, contracts, business, goodwill, data, income, revenue or anticipated savings arising under terms and conditions or in connection with this website, whether direct or indirect, and whether arising in tort, contract, or otherwise.However, nothing in these terms and conditions shall exclude or limit our liability for fraud, for death or personal injury caused by our negligence, or for any other liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.Restricted accessAccess to certain areas of this website is restricted. We reserve the right to restrict access to other areas of this website, or indeed our whole website, at our discretion.If we provide you with a user ID and password to enable you to access restricted areas of this website or other content or services, you must ensure that that user ID and password is kept confidential. You accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your user ID or password.We may disable your user ID and password at our sole discretion or if you breach any of the policies or terms governing your use of this website or any other contractual obligation you owe to us.Entire agreementThese terms and conditions, together with our privacy policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of this website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.Law and jurisdictionThis notice will be governed by and construed in accordance with English law, and any disputes relating to this notice shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England.Privacy PolicyWe are committed to safeguarding the privacy of this website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.(1) What information do we collect?We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:(a) Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views(b) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including email address)(c) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to this website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including email address)(d) Any other information that you choose to send to us.CookiesA cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.We may send a cookie which may be stored on your computer's hard drive. This cookie is only set if you choose to allow your computer to remember your Members Area access details.Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to this website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at:http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.htmlUsing your personal dataPersonal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. We may use your personal information to:(a) Administer the website(b) Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website(c) Enable your use of the services available on the website(d) Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications(e) Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested(f) Send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications (relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties) which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by emailing us.(g) Provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user(h) Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.Other disclosuresIn addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:(a) To the extent that we are required to do so by law(b) In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings(c) In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)(d) To the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.International data transfersInformation that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.Security of your personal dataWe will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.Policy amendmentsWe may update this privacy poli cy from time-to-time by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.Your rightsYou may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)Third party websitesThe website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.Updating informationPlease let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.ContactIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please email them to us.
Explore our
Golf Course
Become a
Member
Visitors
And Societies
Golf
Professionals
